<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PopCornFactory</string>
    <string name="app_desc">Welcome to Popcorn Factory, home of the best series and movies. Just lay down, make some popcorn and enjoy!</string>
    <string name="button">Get me in!</string>
    <string name="titulo">Movies</string>

    <string name="titulo_bones">Bones</string>
    <string name="desc_bones">Dr. Temperance Brennan is a brilliant, but lonely, anthropologist whom is approached by an
                                ambitious FBI agent, named Seely Booth, to help the bureau solve a series of unsolved crimes by
                                identifying the long-dead bodies of missing persons by their bone structure. But both Agent Booth
                                and Dr. Brennan and her team come up again a variety of interference from red tape, corruption,
                                and local noncooperation.
    </string>

    <string name="titulo_drhouse">Dr. House</string>
    <string name="desc_house">The series follows the life of anti-social, pain killer addict, witty and arrogant medical doctor Gregory
                                House (Hugh Laurie) with only half a muscle in his right leg. He and his team of medical doctors try
                                to cure complex and rare diseases from very ill ordinary people in the United States of America.
    </string>

    <string name="titulo_hero">Big Hero 6</string>
    <string name="desc_hero">When a devastating event befalls the city of San Fransokyo and catapults Hiro into the
                                midst of danger, he turns to Baymax and his close friends adrenaline junkie Go Go
                                Tomago, neatnik Wasabi, chemistry whiz Honey Lemon and fanboy Fred. Determined to
                                uncover the mystery, Hiro transforms his friends into a band of high-tech heroes called
                                Big Hero 6.
    </string>

    <string name="titulo_who">Dr. Who</string>
    <string name="desc_who">The series follows the life of anti-social, pain killer addict, witty and arrogant medical doctor Gregory
                            House (Hugh Laurie) with only half a muscle in his right leg. He and his team of medical doctors try
                            to cure complex and rare diseases from very ill ordinary people in the United States of America.
    </string>

    <string name="titulo_friends">Friends</string>
    <string name="desc_friends">Rachel Green, Ross Geller, Monica Geller, Joey Tribbiani, Chandler Bing and Phoebe Buffay are
                                six 20 something year-olds, living off of one another in the heart of New York City. Over the course
                                of ten years, this average group of buddies goes through massive mayhem, family trouble, past and
                                future romances, fights, laughs, tears and surprises as they learn what it really means to be a
                                friend.
    </string>

    <string name="titulo_inception">Inception</string>
    <string name="desc_inception">Dom Cobb is a skilled thief, the absolute best in the dangerous art of extraction, stealing
                                    valuable secrets from deep within the subconscious during the dream state, when the
                                    mind is at its most vulnerable. Cobbs rare ability has made him a coveted player in this
                                    treacherous new world of corporate espionage, but it has also made him an international
                                    fugitive and cost him everything he has ever loved. Now Cobb is being offered a chance at
                                    redemption. One last job could give him his life back but only if he can accomplish the
                                    impossible, inception. Instead of the perfect heist, Cobb and his team of specialists have to
                                    pull off the reverse: their task is not to steal an idea, but to plant one. If they succeed, it
                                    could be the perfect crime. But no amount of careful planning or expertise can prepare the
                                    team for the dangerous enemy that seems to predict their every move. An enemy that only
                                    Cobb could have seen coming.
    </string>

    <string name="titulo_leap">Leap Year</string>
    <string name="desc_leap">A woman who has an elaborate scheme to propose to her boyfriend on Leap Day, an Irish
                            tradition which occurs every time the date February 29 rolls around, faces a major setback
                            when bad weather threatens to derail her planned trip to Dublin. With the help of an
                            innkeeper, however, her cross-country odyssey just might result in her getting engaged.
    </string>

    <string name="titulo_toy">Toy Story</string>
    <string name="desc_toy">Toy Story is about the;secret life of toys; when people are not around. When Buzz
                            Lightyear, a space-ranger, takes Woodys place as Andys favorite toy, Woody doesnt like
                            the situation and gets into a fight with Buzz. Accidentaly Buzz falls out the window and
                            Woody is accused by all the other toys of having killed him. He has to go out of the house
                            to look for him so that they can both return to Andys room. But while on the outside they
                            get into all kind of trouble while trying to get home.
    </string>

    <string name="titulo_small">Smallville</string>
    <string name="desc_small">The numerous miraculous rescues by the local wonder boy Clark have aroused suspicions amongst
                                colonials of Smallville. Interestingly, the boy has managed to downplay his acts of various heroic
                                egresses in the past. They say hes either too fast or has a penchant for finding trouble. He was
                                found by Martha and Jonathan Kent on the day of the Meteor Shower, and subsequently adopted.
                                Clarks friend Lex Luthor, the only heir of Luthorcorp, has been secretly investigating grounds for
                                Clarks outlandish valor. However, on the face of it, Clark just seems a normal boy whos slightly
                                more secretive than usual.
    </string>
</resources>